Morty 学会了开这玩意儿
Learning to fly this thing, Morty,
以后就轻松啦
Is gonna be really liberating.
你就可以随便
You know, you're gonna be free
- 去帮我跑各种活儿了 - 酷
- To go on all kinds of errands for me. - Cool.
看见那颗行星了吗
See that planet right there?
千万别靠太近
Don't fly too close to that planet.
会有人想出来擦你的玻璃窗
Someone will come out and try to wash your windshld.
稍等
Hold on.
在我身上呢
Yeah? Yeah, I have it.
你想在哪儿见面
Where do you want to meet?
好的
All right, cool.
Morty 教学结束了
All right, Morty, lesson's over.
有点事要处理
We got some business to attend to
从这儿往南几光分
A few light minutes south of here.
在太空里还用南边这个说法啊
Oh, you still use south in space?
哇 Jerry
Whoa! Jesus, Jerry!
你在这儿干什么
What the hell are you doing here?!
怎么了
What are you talking about?
我们说好了 如果我儿子要学驾驶
We agreed a boy's father should be present
- 爸爸我必须在场 - 好像是说过
- When he's learning to drive. - I guess I remember that.
你莫非一直都在后座上
Wow. And you've just been back there this whole time?
也是神了
Amazing.
我们没时间把他送回地球了
Well, we don't have time to take him to earth, Morty.
我们去3924917
Head for 3924917.
酷
Cool!
看来我也要跟你们一起来冒险啦
Looks like I'm coming along for an adventure!
嗯哼
Yep.
我们就是要来这儿吗
This is where we're going?
不
Nope.
这儿才是
This is.
你可以停在残障专用车位 Morty
You can park in a handicap spot, Morty.
八条腿以下的生物
Anything with less than eight limbs
在这里都算残疾
Is considered disabled here.
瞧瞧这个小伙子 长得多俊啊
Well, look at this fella. Aren't you handsome?
多谢夸奖
Thank you.
- 我是Jerry - 我知道
- I'm Jerry. - Oh, I know you are.
你是不是坐宇宙飞船来的
Did you come here in a spaceship?
我和儿子岳父一起来的
I'm traveling with my son and father-in-law.
等等 他们不过来吗
W-wait. Are they coming?
他们马上就会回来的
Oh, they'll be back soon.
啥
What?!
这个怎么弄
I don't know how this works!
谁来帮帮我
Help me!
什么鬼东西
What the hell?!
不可理喻 是吧
I know, right?
什么鬼东西
Oh, what the hell?!
不可理喻 对吧
I know, right?
Jerry保育
Jerryboree!?
你给我爸建了一个日托所
You created a day care for my dad?
我倒希望这点子是我想出来的
Are you kidding? I wish I had this idea.
应该说 我确实想到过
Well, I did have this idea,
不过我希望我是握有产权的那个我
But I wish I was the version of me that owned it.
丫可算是发家了
That guy's rich.
记得确认托管的原因
Don't forget to check the reason for your drop-off.
相信我 别的Rick告诉过我
Trust me, Morty, I've heard stories from other ricks.
Jerry离了地球 五分钟也活不下去
Jerrys don't tend to last five minutes off of earth.
这里是一个完全未注册的时间枢纽小行星
This is a totally unregistered cross-temporal asteroid.
可以和其他Jerry一起玩耍嬉戏
Here, they can romp and play with other Jerrys.
再安全不过了
He couldn't be safer.
把这个收好了
Hey, Morty, hang on to this.
上面有你爸的编号
That number's your dad.
要是丢了 他就领不回来了
If you lose it, we're not gonna be able to get him back.
- 在这儿等着 - 我也想去
- Okay, wait here. - I want to come with.
去什么去 很无聊的
Don't come with. It's boring.
我去谈生意
It's it's business stuff.
你在车库里谈什么生意
What kind of business do you do in a garage?
跟见不得人似的
You know, this seems a little shady.
呵呵 你以为见不得人的事情
Right, yeah, like nothing shady ever happened
富丽堂皇的办公室里就没有了吗
In a fully furnished office?
听说过华尔街吗
You ever hear about wall street, Morty?
你知不知道这些人
Y-you know what those guys do
在高档会议室里干什么勾当
In, in, in, their fancy boardrooms?
他们把蛋蛋放进可卡因里
They take their balls and they dip them in cocaine
然后互相蹭过来搅过去
And wipe them all over each other.
外公我行走江湖
You know, grandpa goes around,
做生意都是在大庭广众之下
And he does his business in public,
外公没有什么见不得人的
Because grandpa isn't shady.
妈的
Aw, crap.
嘿
Hey, what's up?
嘿 Rick
Hey, Rick!
来 拿着 三千F币
Here you go. 3,000 flerbos.
武器带来了吧
Do you have the weapon?
咱们能不能稍微
C-can we please?
这是我外孙 Morty
This is my grandson, Morty.
嗨 Morty 我是Krombopulos Michael
Oh, hi, Morty. I'm Krombopulos Michael.
我是个杀手 我从你外公这儿买枪械
I'm an assassin. I buy guns from your grandpa.
给你 你快滚
Here. Go away.
看起来杀伤力很大嘛
Ooh! Yeah, this looks deadly.
这枪射出的是反物质对吧
So, this shoots antimatter?
这次的目标用普通物质可是杀不死的
My target can't be killed with regular matter.
很高兴认识你 Morty
Nice to meet you, Morty.
如果你想弄死任何人
Listen, if you ever need anybody murdered,
请务必联系我
Please give me a call.
- 我从不出岔子 - 你就这么把名片给他了
- I'm very discreet. - You're g-giving him a card?!
我干活没有任何道德标准
I have no code of ethics.
什么地点 什么人都可以
I will kill anyone, anywhere
儿童 动物 老人 都无所谓
Children, animals, old people. Doesn't matter.
杀生就是我的爱好
I just love killing.
你卖武器给杀手来赚钱
You sell weapons to killers for money?
Morty 你这种思维 就是我们星系间
You've got what the intergalactic
所说的典型的拘于世俗
call a very planetary mind-set, Morty.
这些事情比你想的复杂得多
It's more complicated out here.
这些可是F币
These are flerbos.
你知不知道两个人类有了
Do you understand what two humans can accomplish
- 这三千F币能干什么 - 什么
- With 3,000 of these? - Uh, what?
在闪电芯疯狂一下午
An entire afternoon at blips and chitz!
这地方最棒了
Oh, this place is the best.
有啤酒 游戏 奖品
It's got beer, games, prizes,
一玩起来就不知天日
And you can never tell what time it is.
你把枪卖给杀手就为了玩游戏
You sold a gun to a murderer so you could play video games?!
你要是成天就想着怎么玩弄文字
Yeah, sure, I mean, if you spend all day shuffling words around,
什么事儿都能被你说得这么难听
You can make anything sound bad, Morty.
试试这个
Here, check this out.
啊
Aah!
Roy 怎么了
Roy, what's wrong?
我做了个噩梦
I had a nightmare.
跟一个老头在一起
I was with an old man.
他把一头盔戴在了我头上
He put a helmet on me.
是你烧糊涂了 好好休息吧
It's just a fever. Get some sleep.
我可不想让你周一落下课
I don't want you missing school on monday.
我希望你们审视今日
I want you kids to look around you today
然后展望未来
And think about your future.
在这个年纪 你们的人生充满了可能性
Now is the time in your life when anything is possible.
这个球传得太完美了
Spiraling perfectly!
Roy Pasons拿到了球
It's gonna be caught by Roy Parsons!
Roy Parsons过了二十码线
Roy Parsons is at the 20!
过了十码线
Now he's at the 10!
火箭Roy所向披靡
Nothing can stop Roy "The rocket"!
触地得分
Touchdown!
我只是觉得是时候活得现实一些了
I just think it's time to get realistic.
你和我爸谈过地毯店的事了吗
Have you talked to my father about the carpet store?
Roy
Roy?
要是早点发现就好了
Had we caught it sooner well,
不过现在说什么都是马后炮
Had we caught it sooner well, hindsight is 20/20, Roy.
重要的是我们要抓紧治疗
What's important is that we move quickly.
我还不想死
I'm not ready to die.
你不会死的
You're not going to.
火箭不会输给癌症
Roy 地毯很好 谢谢啦
Hey, thanks for the carpet, Roy.
世界上最伟大的爸爸
Roy 你把那些清仓甩卖的波斯白粗毛毯
Hey, Roy, you pulled those persian off-white shags
拿出来了吗
for the clearance sale?
哦 妈的
Whoa. Sh shit!
哦
Oh!
哦 怎么回事
Whoa! What the hell?!
我是在哪儿
W-w-where am I?!
- 到底怎么回事  - 55年 不错嘛 Morty
- What in the hell?! - 55 years. Not bad, Morty.
虽然三十多岁的时候
You kind of wasted your 30s, though,
有点把时间浪费在观鸟上了
with that whole bird-watching phase.
我老婆呢
W-where's my wife?!
Morty 你刚刚只是在玩游戏
Morty, you were just playing a game.
这游戏就叫"Roy"
It's called "Roy."
快清醒点
Snap out of it. Come on.
我是Morty 你是Rick
I'm Morty. You're Rick.
嘿 你卖了把枪给一个杀手
Hey! You sold a gun to a guy that kills people!
癌症你都熬过来了
Look at this, you beat cancer,
居然又回到那个地毯店上班
and then you went back to work at the carpet store?
切
Boo!
不要转换话题 Rick
D-don't dodge the issue, Rick!
卖武器给杀手和自己动手杀人有什么两样
Selling a gun to a hit man is the same as pulling the trigger!
那和什么也不做也没什么两样
It's also the same as doing nothing.
Krombopulos Michael想让谁死
If Krombopulos Michael wants someone dead,
你以为谁能阻止他吗
there's not a lot anyone can do to stop him.
他就是干这一行的
That's why he does it for a living.
不好意思 现在我要碾压你的"Roy"得分了
Now excuse me. It's time to thrash your "Roy" Score.
你本来可以不让这种杀人的事情发生的 Rick
You know, you could stop this killing from happening, Rick!
你就不该卖那把枪
You know, you did a bad thing selling that gun,
只要你愿意 这事是可以挽回的
but you could undo it if you wanted.
嗯哼 这就是我跟你不同的地方了 Morty
Uh-huh, yeah, that's the difference between you and me, Morty.
我是绝不会回地毯店去的
I never go back to the carpet store.
天啦 这家伙要让Roy隐居山林
Holy shit! This guy's taking Roy off the grid!
他的Roy连社保号都不要了
This guy doesn't have a social security number for Roy!
你好 打扰一下
Hi. I'm sorry.
我想 这里是不是有点小误会
I think there was a misunderstanding.
我是个成年人 我想回家
I'm an adult and would like to go home, please.
哦 当然可以 从那个管道出去就行
Well, of course. Right through that tube.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
你做得很好
You're doing great.
钻根管子而已 我会的好吧
I know how to crawl in a tube.
真是
Come on.
哦
Oh.
这比看起来要难
This is harder than it looks.
嗷
Whoa!
- 马可 - 波罗(类似于瞎子摸鱼的游戏)
- Marco? - Polo!
马可
Marco?
来找我呀
Come find me.
马可
Marco?
你们玩得很高兴吗
You guys are enjoying this?
就不觉得有点被当成小孩子在哄着
Don't you feel a little patronized?
怎么会呢
How so?
- Jerry - Beth.
- Jerry! - Beth.
这也太扯了
Oh, come on. This is ridiculous.
Jerry 我爱你
I love you, Jerry.
哦 Beth
Aw, Beth.
谁想看"午夜狂奔"
Who wants to come watch "Midnight run"
带导演评论的
with director's commentary on?
好啊 当然想看
Yeah! Definitely.
第一个来的可以调节画面设置哦
First one there gets to adjust the picture setting!
出厂设置里色调总是设得太高
The factory tint setting is always too high!
- 快让开 - 色调总是设得太高
- Out of my way. - The tint setting is always too high.
我又要去杀人啦
Oh, boy. Here I go killing again.
您已到达Krombopulos Michael所在地
You have arrived at Krombopulos Michael.
目标位于下方
Your destination is below.
波斯白地毯都卖完了
We're all out of off-white persian.
天哪 我都做了什么
Oh, man! W-w-what have I done?!
- 放下武器  - 不是你想的那样
- Drop the gun. - You don't understand!
这个人是来杀人的
This guy was gonna kill someone!
那要杀人的就不止他一个了
I guess that makes two of us.
啊
Aah!
你在做什么 Morty
What are you doing, Morty?
这里是星系联邦的哨站
This is a galactic federation outpost!
没空跟你把来龙去脉讲清楚了
Look, I don't have time to tell you my entire backstory,
但你外公我跟政府合不来
but grandpa and government don't get along.
他救了我一命
He saved my life.
- 什么 - 啊 哦
- What? - Huh?! Whoa!
你是Krombopulos Michael的目标吗
Are you Krombopulos Michael's target?
你叫什么名字
W-what's your name?
我的种族用不上名字
My kind has no use for names.
我们交流的方式是你所谓"Jessica的脚"
I communicate through what you call "Jessica's feet"
不 是"心灵感应"
No, "Telepathy."
真棒啊 Morty
Oh, good job, Morty.
你弄死了我最好的客户
Y-you killed my best customer,
就救了一个会读心术的屁
but you saved a mind-reading fart.
屁 这个名字我喜欢
I like this name fart.
Morty 你能好心拉一下
Morty, would you kindly release me
监牢左边的控制杆 把我放出来吗
by pulling that lever to the left of my cell?
我很痛苦
I am in great pain.
Morty 不要
Morty, don't do it.
Morty
Morty...
Morty 你个蠢蛋
Morty, you idiot.
糟了 我们得赶紧带你走
Oh, crap. Let's get you out of here!
我们带不走他的 他是气体
We can't get him out of here. He's gaseous.
他过不了传送门 Morty
He's not gonna make it through a portal, Morty.
那我们就只好都上车了
Well, then, I guess we're all getting in the car.
- 对吧 呃  - 叫我屁就好
- Right, uh... - fart.
不是 赶紧上车
No! Just j-just get in the car!
Morty 别这样 我想回闪电芯
Morty, come on. I want to go back to Blips and Chitz.
这事儿我不想应付
I don't want to deal with this.
Rick 既然你态度这么明确
Rick, you've been clear on the fact
不想帮忙 那就走开
that you don't want to help, so just go away.
更多人在赶来
More are coming.
管你的 我走了
Screw this. I'm out.
哦 快点 快点
Whoa! Come on, come on!
滚出那个垃圾做的飞船 不然我们就开枪了
Get out of the vehicle made of garbage or we will open fire!
开枪
Open fire!
蠢[哔]地毯店的救屁主
Stupid-ass, fart-saving, carpet-store mother[bleep]
挪开
Move!
你[哔]的动了我调好的座位吗
Wait, did you with my seat settings?
更多人要来了
More are coming.
Rick
Rick!
嗯 嗯
Yeah, yeah.
你的盖尔顿转换器坏得真厉害
Your geldon convertor is pretty dinged up.
因为我孙子开飞船开得像个雄性的Obradian
That's because my grandson drives like a male Obravadian.
我就开地图炮了 有些所谓偏见纯属事实如此
Yeah, I said it. Some stereotypes are based in fact.
其实是因为常年失修
Actually, it's because of years of neglect.
你真的需要尊重一下这些齿轮 Rick
You really need to respect your gears, Rick.
对你而言 它们只是带齿的轮子
To you, they're just wheels with teeth,
然而在我们的文化里 是有战争
but in my culture, wars have been fought...
我听过了 你只管修好就是
So I've heard. Just fix it.
那些Gromflamite应该暂时找不到我们
I don't think the Gromflamites can track us now,
但我们应该得在这待一段时间
but it looks like we're gonna be here for a while.
或者 如果你拿了K. Michael掉的那把枪
Or, you know, if you still have that gun K. Michael dropped,
我们可以直接把他的活儿给干了 然后回家
we could finish the job and go home.
你是知道我会读心术的吧
You do understand I'm telepathic, right?
我这是礼貌
I'm being polite.
Rick 我们得把他带回他归属的地方
Rick, we're taking him back where he belongs.
是吗 那是哪里
Oh, yeah? Where's that?
你是要去找出是谁放了这个屁吗
Are you going on a quest to find he who smelt it?
我不小心通过一个虫洞来到这里
I came here accidentally through a wormhole
那个虫洞位于 你们所谓的"滚出我的脑袋 屁
located in what you call "Get out of my head, fart.
我知道你在读心 啦啦啦啦"
I know you're in here. La-la-la-la "
不 它位于你们所谓的 普罗米修斯星云
No, in what you call the Promethean Nebula.
哦 真好 只要蹦一下跳一下 再蹿个800光年就到了
Oh, great. Just a hop, skip, and an 800-light-year jump.
Rick 你想走的话 随时可以走
You know, you can leave anytime you want, Rick.
不管你了 你这个小废逼
Whatever you want to do, you little punk-ass little bitch.
谢谢你 Morty
Thank you, Morty.
你和其他的碳基生命不一样
You are not like other carbon-based life-forms.
你把其他的生命看的比自己重要
You put the value of all life above your own.
就应该是这样
It's how things should be.
就可以是这样
It's how they could be.
我完全赞同
I could not agree more.
*四海一家*
*The worlds can be one together*
*宇宙和谐*
*Cosmos without hatred*
*你眼中星光亮如宝石*
*Stars like diamonds in your eyes*
*大地即是太空*
*The ground can be space space space space space*
*双足迈向平静的天穹*
*with feet marching towards a peaceful sky*
*所有的月中人都想事事如他所愿*
*All the moon men want things their way*
*但我们一定要让他们看到太阳*
*But we make sure they see the sun*
*再见吧 月中人*
*Goodbye, moon men*
*说再见吧 月中人*
*You say goodbye, moon men*
*再见*
*Goodbye*
别再唱[哔]月球人了
Shut the [bleep] up about moon men!
又不是在表演音乐剧
This isn't a musical number.
我们现在要[哔]
This is a [bleep] operation.
冷静 行事低调
We got to be cool and [bleep] lay low.
duck duck goose是儿童游戏
birdie双关小鸟和高尔夫中的小鸟球
鸭子 鸭子 小鸟(球)
Duck, duck, birdie?
太逗了
That's very funny!
还有更逗的呢
Here comes another funny.
噢 这地方太赞了
Oh, this place is great.
我都快希望能多待两天了
I almost wish I could stay longer than one day.
有可能哦
You just might.
啥意思
W-what do you mean?
这些是Rick和Morty再也没回来接走的Jerry
These are the Jerrys whose Ricks and Mortys never came back.
他们长住在这儿了
They live here now.
关于身份不明的人状人逃犯的离奇案件
No gear-turnings as of yet in the curious case
至今仍未有进展
Of these unidentified humanoid fugitives,
据报道 逃犯仍在逃于齿轮系统某处
Reportedly at large somewhere within the gear system.
他妈的
Son of a...
为什么那些Gromfalmite要囚禁你
Why were the Gromflamites holding you prisoner?
你[哔]为什么这么重要
What the [bleep] is so valuable about you?
我并不比生命更珍贵
I am no more valuable than life itself.
不过 我能够改变原子的构成
However, I am able to alter the composition of atoms,
就像这样
Like this.
这原本是氧原子
That was oxygen.
我给它加了71个质子
I added 71 protons to it.
不得了啊 这屁能拉金
Terrific. The fart that pooped gold.
怪不得系统里的每个条子都在找我们
No wonder every cop in the system is looking for us.
任何物种只要控制了这一股屁
Any species that gets ahold of this thing
就可以利用它来统治银河系了
Is gonna use it to take over the galaxy.
你知道这样会给我的工作带来多大的不方便吗
You know how inconvenient that's gonna be to my work?
有人把我们卖了
Somebody dropped the dime on us.
机头
Gearhead!
抱歉 Rick
I'm sorry, Rick.
抓住你的赏金太高了
The reward on your head is too high.
就像你经常说的
And like you always say,
人不为己 天诛地灭
You got to look out for number one.
该诛的是不为老子做事的人
Number one is me, asshole!
我们该是一伙儿的
You're supposed to be my friend!
一伙儿的 那你知道我的真名吗
Friend?! Do you even know my real name?
是小Revolio Clockberg
It's Revolio Clockberg Junior.
我是齿轮人中的一员
I belong to an entire species of gear people.
叫我"机头"
Calling me "Gearhead"
就等于管一个中国人叫"黄脸佬"
Is like calling a chinese person "Asia face."
别 别扔树枝
No! Not twigs!
有两点 你们全都给我搞清楚
Two things I want to make clear to everybody in this room
一 永远也别背叛我 二 该走了
Never betray me, and it's time to go.
不许动
Nobody move!
噢天 那不会是
Oh, my god. Are those...
嘿 Morty 记得你说过
Hey, Morty, remember when you said
卖枪和亲自扣扳机没两样吗
Selling a gun was as bad as pulling the trigger?
因为你做的选择
How do you feel about all these people
现在死了这么多人 你有何感想啊
That are getting killed today because of your choices?
我没做错 Rick
I did the right thing, Rick!
- 这话你和机头的机蛋说去吧  - 明明是你下的手
- Tell that to Gearhead's Gearsticles. - You did that!
呵呵 这个时候我本来该在玩"Roy"
Wrong! I'd be playing "Roy" right now.
Morty 事情发展到这一步 我也别无他法
At a certain point, my hands are tied, Morty.
难以置信Rick能干出这种事
I can't believe Rick did this.
- 这是第八根压死骆驼的最后稻草了 - 我预下
- This is the eighth to the last straw. - Ante up.
去他的
You know what? Screw it!
咱们赌点更大的吧
I have a better gamble for you guys.
咱越狱
I say we escape.
你要是想走 可以从前门出去
If you want to leave, you can just go out the front door.
你以为我们留在这儿是被逼的吗
You think we're kept here against our will?
那样是违法的
That would be illegal.
但如果你们可以走的话 你们还留在这儿干嘛
But if you can leave, then why are you still here?
和你一样
Same reason as you.
因为我们是Jerry
We're Jerrys.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
好的呀 随时都可以走哟
Okay, then. That was always allowed.
Morty 你来开
Morty, take the wheel!
哇 哇
Whoa! Whoa!
天啊 搞什么鬼啊 Morty
Geez! Damn it, Morty!
谁教会你开这玩意儿的
Who taught you to fly this thing?
开玩笑的 知道是我教的
I'm kidding. I know that's on me.
嗯 Rick
Um, Rick!
妈的
Shit.
这下看来是完蛋了
Well, I guess this is it.
Morty 开窗
Morty, crack the window.
我想知道为什么Greg整天挑我女朋友的刺儿
I wonder why Greg is always so critical of my girlfriend.
嗯 他可能就是吃醋了 想一个人占着我
Well, he'd probably like to have me to himself.
朋友之间都是这样的啦
That's how friends are.
还是他想占着她呢
Or does he want her to himself?
*世界可以融为一体*
*The worlds can be one together*
*宇宙本无仇恨*
*Cosmos without hatred*
*星星如你双眸中钻石般闪烁*
*Stars like diamonds in your eyes*
我的人生就[哔]是个笑话
My life is a [bleep] joke!
*再见 月中人*
*Goodbye, moon men*
*说再见吧 月中人*
*You say goodbye, moon men*
*再见 月中人*
*Goodbye, moon men*
好了 我们出发吧
All right. Let's preceed.
靠
Damn.
真是怪不到别人头上了
Can't blame that on the dog.
要说没动静又杀得多
Talk about silent but deadly.
我是见识过某些神经毒气
I-I've seen some nerve gas,
但是这团气才是够神够精啊
But that this gas got nerve!
懂我在说啥吧
You know what I'm saying?
- 说够了没  - Morty 说够了我会吱一声的
- Are you done? - I'll let you know, Morty.
死人天上"屁-嗷"啊
Gone with the wind! Am I right?!
Morty 不喜欢这梗啊
If you don't like that one, Morty,
那这个怎么样 "开杀布兰卡"
An alt on that could be, like, if I said "Gasablanca"!
好了 不玩了
All right, I'm done.
我们去普罗米修斯星云吧
Let's get to the Promethean Nebula,
我孙子拯救生命之旅就能结束啦
So my grandson can finish saving a life!
麻烦来一张去地球的票
Um, earth, please?
就这个 我要给钱吗
Is this? Do I pay?
噢 不好意思 不好意思
Oh, I'm sorry, sorry!
噢 嘿 什么
Oh, uh, hey. What?
啊 你想干嘛
Uh, what do you want?
嘿 你不是走了吗
Hey. Are you the one that left?
明白了
I get it.
外面的世界太乱了
It's a it's a hassle out there.
对吧 谁要出去啊
Right? And who needs that?
对吧 对吧
Right? Right?
- 我不要出去  - 谁要啊
- Not me. - Who needs that?
反正不是我们
Ho, ho! Not us.
你是谁
Uh, who are you?
噢 不好意思 Paul Fleischman
Oh, excuse me. Paul Fleischman.
无限的时间线
Infinite timelines.
在某些时间线里 Beth再婚了
In some of them, Beth remarries.
- 天啊  - 不要担心
- Geez. - Don't worry.
我对Beth非常好哦
I treat Beth very well,
我和Morty的关系保持得很有分寸
And I do not overstep my bounds with Morty.
每个孩子都需要父亲 但你是无法替代的
Every kid needs a dad, but there's no replacing you.
嘿 你想来帮一下忙吗
Hey, you want to give us a hand with this?
我们想听音箱 而不是让声音
We're trying to figure out how to get the sound
直接从电视出来
Coming through the stereo instead of the tv.
很难搞哎
I-I-it's very difficult.
噢 有辅助输入端吗
Oh! Uh, well, is there an aux input?
我们试过了 但是有两种不同颜色的接口
We tried that, but there's two different colors.
但是有两种不同的颜色
But there's two different colors.
虫洞距离你所谓"这里"的
The wormhole is 70 of what you call "Meters"
所谓"南边" 还有70 所谓的 "米"
What you call "North" Of what you call "Here."
好吧 Morty 把你的屁塞回那个洞 道个别吧
Fine. Morty, take your fart to his hole and say your goodbyes.
我去加点油 顺便拉一大坨Morty
I'm gonna find some fuel and take a big, fat Morty.
今天这些事以后 "Morty"现在是我对便便的新说法
That's my new word for shit because of today's events.
就是这儿了
Here it is.
这能让我回到我的族类身边
This should take me back to my kind.
屁 我会想你的
I'm gonna miss you, um, fart.
我很抱歉你的名字成了"屁"
I'm really sorry your name became fart.
- Morty 我很快会回来了  - 真的吗
- I will be back soon, Morty. - Really?
等我回到我的同类身边之后
After I return to the others with this location,
我们会回来净化你们的
We will be back for your cleansing.
嗯 净化
Um, cleansing?
碳基生物对所有高等生物来说都是威胁
Carbon-based life is a threat to all higher life.
你对于我们来说 就好比你们所谓的疾病
To us, you are what you would call a disease.
无论我们在哪里发现你们 我们都会将其治愈
Wherever we discover you, we cure it.
你自己也说过 生命必须得到保护
You said yourself that life must be protected,
即使是以牺牲为代价
Even though sacrifice.
你还没有改变你的想法
You haven't changed your mind about that.
我能感觉到
I can sense your thoughts.
Morty
Morty?
嗯 在你离开之前 你可以
Um, before you go, could you sing a
你可以再为我唱一次歌吗
C-could you sing for me again?
Morty 当然可以
Yes, morty.
*宇宙本无仇恨*
*Cosmos without hatred*
*钻石星辰闪耀着宇宙光泽*
*Diamond stars with cosmic light*
*类星体在这永夜中闪耀*
*Quasars shine through endless night*
*在绮丽壮美中万物归一*
*And everything is one in the beauty*
*现在我们该告别了
*And now we say goodbye*
啊
Aah!
Morty 为什么 为什么要这样做
Morty, why? Why?
再见
Goodbye.
你们两个是不是缠绵不休 难舍难分呵
So, did you guys make out a little bit?
他要寄明信片给你吗
Is he gonna send you a postcard?
那家伙碰上你简直像中了彩票呀
Man, that guy hit the lottery when he crossed paths with you.
Morty 虽然我今天一直嫌弃
Morty, I know I picked on your core beliefs
你的原则和你的各种决策
And decisions making a lot today,
但是我很高兴你坚持
But I am glad that you insisted
把那屁送回了家
On getting that fart home.
至少所有这些死伤和破坏
You know, at least all the death and destruction
没有白费 对吧
Wasn't for nothing, you know?
你开始想念你的屁友了吗 哈
You miss your fart friend, huh?
我为你准备了一份惊喜哟
Well, I got a little surprise for you, buddy.
你走之后 我找到了一个新的虫洞
While you were gone, I found a new wormhole
洞的另一边有成千上万这样的气体
With millions of beings just like him on the other side,
他们都准备要来拜访了
And they're all coming to visit.
什么 Rick 不要 不要这样
What?! Rick, no! You can't!
太迟了 Morty 那个洞已经开了
Too late, Morty. The hole's opening.
不是啊 Rick 你不明白
No, Rick! You don't understand.
里面还有更多哦
There's- there's a lot more where that came from, too.
嘿 嘿 兄弟
Hey, hey, bro,
你的Morty今天害死了多少人啊
how many people was your Morty responsible for killing today?
一个都没有 我们今天一整天都在闪电芯玩得很开心
None. We chilled at Blips and Chitz all day.
是吧 兄弟
Ain't that right, homey?
对啊 哥们 "Roy"万岁
Darn right, bro! "Roy" Rules!
肯定很好玩
Must be nice.
嘿 Morty 我们的Jerry在那边
Hey, Morty, there's our Jerry.
我好想你 嘿 Rick
Mm! I missed you. Hey, Rick.
好高兴看到你平安无事 Jerry
Glad you're safe, Jerry.
- 回家怎么样  - 好极了
- What do you say we go home? - I'd like that.
嘿 等一下 你们的是5126吗
Hey, wait. Uh, do you have 5126?
不确定哎 Morty
Uh, I'm not sure. Morty.
那是一张闪电芯的票
Uh, that's a Blips and Chitz ticket.
- 什么 - 瞧瞧你 Morty
- What?! - Way to go, Morty.
算了 随便吧
Eh, whatever.
- 等一下 什么 - 等一下 什么
- Uh, w-wait. What? - Uh, w-wait. What?
- 走吧 Jerry - 走吧 Jerry
- Come on, Jerry. All right. - Come on, jerry.
无聊的生活 你厌倦了吗
Are you tire of the same daily droll?
来闪电芯狂欢吧
Well, get on over to Blips and Chitz!
这儿有一游戏
We got, uh, one game.
这里有一大堆游戏
We got a whole bunch of games here.
吃的有有恰宝 还有弗宝
You can, we got Chabos and Flobos,
你可以射击
And you can shoot things!
来我们这儿玩游戏吧
Get over here! Play the games!
用你的F币来换票
Uh, use your flerbos to get tickets!
"Roy 2"来啦
"Roy 2" Just got here.
来精芯玩个痛快吧
Get over here at Jitz and Chitz!
这是世界上最酷的地方
It's the coolest place in the world.
我上广告啦
Uh, I get to be in the commercial!